Ramon Carlo Evidente

Scarborough Ontario, 50 Tweedrock Crescent, M1E 4L5 Contact Info: 647-997-9748, carloevidente@hotmail.com

Objective

To acquire a job at a respected company to expand my knowledge, talents, and learnings. Obtain a responsible employment opportunity that will allow me to make the most of my education and experience while significantly contributing to the company's success.

Skills

- Initiative
- Customer Service
- Able to multitask
- Merchandising

- Cashier
- Quick learner
- Outgoing
- Fast and efficient

Work Experience

Shoppers Drug Mart - Scarborough. Ontario | February 2022- November 2022 Merchandiser

- Communicated and provided service to customers
- Checked off items for picklist, and sent them out to merchandise
- Scanned items that were overstock into inventory

Tim Hortons - Scarborough, Ontario | April 2023 - July 2023

Crew Member

- Welcomed customers and helped prepare their order
- Taking payments for food orders and providing the correct change
- Assembled and served meals/drinks according to specific guest requirements.

Volunteer Experience

St John Paul II - Scarborough, Ontario 2022-2023 Tutored Students

- Assisted grade 10 students with science and history homework/assignments
- Used communication, organization, and quick-thinking skills to find efficient ways to teach students
- Composed a lesson plan to teach students/to help them study

Education and Training

St John Paul II - Scarborough, Ontario 2019- 2023

Ontario Secondary School Diploma

Centennial College - Scarborough, Ontario 2023-Current

Ontario College Advanced Diploma

Accomplishments

- Consistent Honor Roll Grade 8-12
- Cooperative Education Academic Award Grade 11